localrecruit.co.uk 2015-06-07

# Local Recruit: Privacy Policy

Local Jobs From The UK's Leading Jobs Sites Sorted By Town 

## Privacy Policy

Within this Privacy Policy the term 'Local Recruit.co.uk' covers all sites owned and run through the LocalRecruit network, and sites owned by Blue Splodge i Ltd.

LocalRecruit.co.uk is committed to protecting your privacy and this Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information through our web site. "Personal Information" means information that would allow a party to contact you, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number, or email address.

The Policy is changed occasionally so please make sure you review this Policy from time to time.

## How Data is Collected

We collect Personal Information about you when you submit information or requests to us (through this website or otherwise). We use your submitted information to send you emails that you have requested, to send your job application to the requested third party when you apply to certain jobs on our web site, and to improve the search functionality on our web site. In emails we send you, we provide a method to unsubscribe from future emails.

When you submit your email address as part of our Jobs By Email application, we only use this address to email you the job alerts that you requested. Your email address is deleted from our database when you remove/unsubscribe from the Job By Email alert service.

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Browsing of Data

When you use the LocalRecruit.co.uk site, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically while visiting our site, including the web pages you view and the times you view them and information about the browser you are using.  We do not link this information to the Personal Information you submit to us; we use this browsing information to personalise aspects of your search experience and for internal purposes such as site improvements. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session.

## What are "Cookies" and how are they used?

Please refer to our Cookie Policy for full infomation about the cookies we use and what they do.

With regards to Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) (used to serve ads on this site):

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

## Disclosure of Data

Although we may disclose aggregated information about the use of our site, that information does not contain Personal Information. We do not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations other than sending your job application to the third party when you apply to certain jobs on our web site. Under certain circumstances, however, we could be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties and if LocalRecruit.co.uk becomes part of another organisation, that organisation will possess the Personal Information collected by LocalRecruit.co.uk and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

## Data Security

LocalRecruit.co.uk has implemented and follows industry standard measures to protect against unauthorised access to and processing of Personal Information. We do our utmost however no site can fully remove all risk.

## Any Questions?

We are very happy to receive any queries, comments, or requests you may have regarding our Privacy Policy.  Feel free and do not hesitate to contact us.
